Detective: ÔIŐve found where she lives,Ő
Reader: said the detective quietly.
Detective: ÔHere is the address.Ő
Reader: Hartley took the piece of paper.
On it were the words,
ÔVivienne Arlington, number 341 East 49th Street.Ő
Detective: ÔShe moved there a week ago,Ő
Reader: said the detective.
Detective: ÔI can follow her if you want.
It will only cost you 7 dollars a day and expensesÉŐ
Hartley: ÔNo, thank you,Ő
Reader: interrupted Hartley.
Hartley: ÔI only wanted the address.
How much is it?Ő
Detective: ÔOne dayŐs work,Ő
Reader: said the detective.
Detective: ÔTen dollars.Ő
Reader: Hartley paid the man.
Then he left his office and took a tram to Broadway.
After walking a short distance, he arrived at the building that he was looking for.
He went up the stairs into her apartment and saw her standing by the window.
Vivienne was about 21.
Her hair was red gold, and her eyes were sea-blue.
She was wearing a white top and a dark skirt.
Hartley: ÔVivienne,Ő
Reader: said Hartley angrily,
Hartley: Ôyou didnŐt answer my last letter.
It took me a week to find your new address!
Why didnŐt you answer me?
You knew I was waiting to see you and hear from you.Ő